{
    "id": "f9ab01be1a68480db1ac8e3e780728ed",
    "title": "Active And Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "They are preparing the report. / The report …………………………….. by them.",
            "description": "In the present continuous tense, the passive form is made with is/are/am + being + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "is prepared",
                "was prepared",
                "is being prepared"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "They took the child to hospital. / The child ………………………….. to hospital.",
            "description": "In the simple past tense, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "was taken",
                "has taken",
                "is taken"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She answered the question. / The question ………………………….. by her.",
            "description": "In the simple past tense, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "is answered",
                "was answered",
                "has answered"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She has written four novels. / Four novels ……………………………. by her.",
            "description": "In the present perfect tense, the passive form is made with has/have + been + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "were written",
                "have written",
                "have been written"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The chief guest gave away the prizes. / The prizes …………………………….. by the chief guest.",
            "description": "In the simple past tense, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "are given",
                "were given",
                "have been given"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The dacoit killed the traveler. / The traveler …………………………. by the dacoit.",
            "description": "In the simple past tense, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "has killed",
                "was killed",
                "had killed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They robbed him at gunpoint. / He …………………………… at gunpoint.",
            "description": "In the simple past tense, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "is robbed",
                "was being robbed",
                "was robbed"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He has won a lottery. / A lottery …………………………. by him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was won",
                "has been won",
                "had been won"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They made all the furniture out of teak. / All the furniture …………………………. out of teak.",
            "description": "In the simple past tense, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "has been made",
                "was made",
                "had made"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She called me a liar. / I ……………………………… a liar.",
            "description": "In the simple past tense, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "called",
                "am called",
                "was called"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He sells newspapers at the railway station. / Newspapers ………………………………… by him.",
            "description": "In the simple present tense, the passive form is made with is/am/are + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "are sold",
                "have sold",
                "are being sold"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He bought the painting at an auction. / The painting …………………………… at an auction.",
            "description": "In the simple past tense, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "has bought",
                "was bought",
                "had been bought"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}